Liberian Government Archives II, 1911-1968 LCP2006/003
Liberian Collections
- Executive, 1911-1968 (Box 1)
  - Executive Mansion (Box 1)
    - Domestic Correspondence - Departmental (Box 1)
      - Western Province Voinjama-Kolahun District Radiograms, July-December 1941; 70 Items (Box 6)
      - Justice, 1931-1943; 8 Items (Box 6)
      - Attorney General, 1912-1918; 24 Items (Box 6)
      - Attorney General, 1931-1943; 29 Items (Box 6)
      - Attorney General Report on Special Mission to Maryland County, 1940; 109 pp. (Box 6)
      - Bureau of Immigration, 1931-1940; 14 Items (Box 6)
      - Maryland County Justice Officials, 1917-1934; 5 Items (Box 6)
      - Monsterrado County Sherriff, 1915; 1 Item (Box 6)
      - Sinoe County Justice Officials, 1913-1915; 7 Items (Box 6)
      - Sinoe County Justice Officials, 1937-1943; 17 Items (Box 6)
      - Postmaster General, 1916; 1930-1939; 12 Items (Box 6)
      - Department of Public Instruction, 1920-1932; 5 Items (Box 6)
      - Department of Public Instruction, 1936-1939; 12 Items (Box 6)
      - State, 1912; 32 Items (Box 6)
      - State, 1914-1919; 15 Items (Box 6)
      - State, October 1920-January 1925; 19 Items (Box 6)
      - State, February-March 1925; 11 Items (Box 6)
      - State, June-July 1925; 24 Items (Box 6)
      - State, August-October 1925 (Box 6)
      - State, November-December 1925; 16 Items (Box 6)
      - State, 1926-1929; 3 Items (Box 6)
      - State, 1930-1936; 33 Items (Box 6)
      - State, 1937; 52 Items (Box 6)
      - State, 1938-1942; 10 Items (Box 7)
      - State, 1953-1966; 10 Items (Box 7)
      - Secretary of State, 1920-1929; 23 pp. (Box 7)
        [HT]
      - Treasury, January-August 1912; 13 Items (Box 7)
      - Treasury, September-December 1912; 16 Items (Box 7)
      - Treasury, May 1914-June 1915; 35 Items (Box 7)
      - Treasury, July-December 1915; 16 Items (Box 7)
      - Treasury, 1923-1930; 6 Items (Box 7)
      - Treasury, 1931-1934; 13 Items (Box 7)
      - Treasury, 1935-1936; 16 Items (Box 7)
      - Treasury, November 1937; 59 Items (Box 7)
      - Treasury, August-September 1939; 15 Items (Box 7)
      - Bureau of Audits, 1935-1942; 25 Items (Box 7)
      - Bureau of Internal Revenue, 1912-1930; 23 Items (Box 7)
      - Bureau of Internal Revenue, 1932-1937; 18 Items (Box 7)
      - Bureau of Revenues, 1938-1939; 6 Items (Box 7)
      - Customs Receivership, 1914-1931; 1940; 19 Items (Box 7)
      - Executive Office Receipts, 1915-1916; 37 Items (Box 7)
      - Financial Advisor, 1930-1935; 10 Items (Box 7)
      - Financial Advisor, 1936-1937; 22 Items (Box 7)
      - Financial Advisor, 1939-1943; 6 Items (Box 7)
      - Financial Advisor, January-February 1938; 24 Items (Box 7)
      - Financial Advisor, March-April 1938; 19 Items (Box 7)
      - Mining Bureau re: Western Province, April 1941; 2 Items (Box 7)
      - Secretary of Treaury re: Grand Cape Mount, 1941; 2 Items (Box 7)
      - Report of the Gola Uprising, 1919; 45 pp. (Box 7)
      - War, 1912-1914; 14 Items (Box 7)
      - War, 1915; 17 Items (Box 7)
      - War, 1916; 32 Items (Box 7)
      - War, 1917-1919; 18 Items (Box 7)
      - War, 1920-1923; 6 Items (Box 7)
      - War, 1924-1928; 16 Items (Box 7)
      - War, 1931-1933; 20 Items (Box 7)
      - War, January-May 1934; 13 Items (Box 7)
      - War, June 1934; 18 Items (Box 7)
      - War, July 1934-1935; 12 Items (Box 7)
      - War, 1936-1943; 20 Items (Box 7)
      - Vice-President, 1937; 9 Items (Box 7)
    - Domestic Correspondence - Judicial (Box 7)
      - Maryland County Circuit Court, 1928 (Box 7)
      - Sinoe County Circuit Court, 1925; 2 Items (Box 7)
      - Supreme Court, 1916; 5 Items (Box 7)
      - Supreme Court, 1937; 2 Items (Box 7)
      - Legislature, 1915-1930; 33 Items (Box 7)
      - Legislature, 1931-1935; 13 Items (Box 7)
      - Legislature, 1936; 29 Items (Box 7)
      - Legislature, 1937; 80 Items (Box 7)
      - Legislature, 1938-1944; 33 Items (Box 7)
    - Foreign Correspondence (Box 7)
      - 1912-1920, 27 Items (Box 7)
      - 1921-1929, 29 Items (Box 7)
      - 1930-1935, 11 Items (Box 7)
      - 1936-1938, 31 Items (Box 7)
      - 1939-1951, 12 Items (Box 7)
      - France, 1924 (Box 7)
      - Germany, 1929 (Box 7)
      - Great Britain, 1924 (Box 7)
      - League of Nations, 1930-1932; 5 Items (Box 7)
        [PC & MS]
      - League of Nations, Special Commissioner to Kru Coast, 1932; 24 Items (Box 7)
      - France/Fernando Po, 1929; 3 Items (Box 7)
      - United States., 1932-1934; 3 Items (Box 7)
    - Cabinet Minutes (Box 8)
      - Cabinet Minutes and Memoranda, 1916-1918; 4 Items (Box 8)
    - Conferences (Box 8)
      - Bopulu Conference Report, 22-24 January 1935; 34 pp. (Box 8)
      - Bopulu-Suehn Conference Minutes, 12-21 October 1942; 118 pp. (Box 8)
      - Bopulu-Suehn Conference Minutes, 5-16 July 1941; 133 pp. (Box 8)
      - Conference Decision of Gissi Chiefs vs. Commissioner Reeves, 10 December 1934; 11 pp. (Box 8)
      - Greenville Conference with Chiefs, 2-7 April 1937; 10 Items (Box 8)
      - Jedeh Conference with Chiefs, 4-12 January 1938; 39 pp. (Box 8)
      - Juarzon Conference with Chiefs, 11 May 1937; 4 Items (Box 8)
      - Kakata Conference with Chiefs, 16 January-25 February 1939; 4 Items (Box 8)
      - Kolahun Conference Minutes Part I, 21 July - 11 August 1941; 100 pp. (Box 8)
      - Kolahun Conference Minutes Part II, 21 July - 11 August 1941; 92 pp. (Box 8)
      - Kolahun Conference Minutes Part III, 21 July - 11 August 1941; 51 pp. (Box 8)
      - Kolahun Conference Report Part I, 8-23 January 1937; 101 pp. (Box 8)
      - Kolahun Conference Report Part II, 8-23 January 1937; 99 pp. (Box 8)
      - Kolahun Conference Report, 4-8 February 1935; 48 pp. (Box 8)
      - Naarma Conference Report, 27 February 1935; 9 pp. (Box 8)
      - Report on Tewar Garwular Council, 16 June 1941; 34 pp. (Box 8)
      - Saniquelle Conference with Chiefs from Districts 2 and 3, 16-28 March 1925; 9 Items (Box 8)
      - Sasstown Conference with Chiefs, 23-28 April 1937; 10 pp. (Box 8)
      - Secretary of Interior Holder's Tour - Appendices, June-September 1941; 65 pp. (Box 8)
      - Tewo District Council with Chiefs, March-April 1926; 10 Items (Box 8)
      - Timbo Conference with Chiefs from Chiefdom 4, 21 May-3 June 1937; 2 Items (Box 8)
      - Voinjama Boundary Dispute Wonnegomai v. Bondi-Wubomai, 1-4 December 1936; 18 pp. (Box 8)
      - Voinjama Conference Minutes, 14-16 August 1941; 26 pp. (Box 8)
      - Voinjama Conference with Chiefs, 27 January-2 February 1937; 64 pp. (Box 8)
      - Voinjama-Kolahun Women and School Children Reports, 27-28 August 1941; 2 Items (Box 8)
        [PC[
      - Western Province Conference with Chiefs, 11-13 January 1943; 4 Items (Box 8)
      - Zorzor Conference Minutes Part I, 19 August-17 September 1941; 100 pp. (Box 8)
      - Zorzor Conference Minutes Part II, 19 August-17 September 1941; 100 pp. (Box 8)
      - Zorzor Conference Minutes Part III, 19 August-17 September 1941; 85 pp. (Box 8)
      - Zorzor Conference Report, 18-25 February 1935; 62 pp. (Box 8)
      - Zorzor Conference with Chiefs, 5-8 February 1937; 37 pp. (Box 8)
    - Presidential Commissions (Box 8)
      - Executive Commission to Grand Bassa, 1924 (Box 8)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary, 1920-1926; 25 Items (Box 8)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary, 1926-1927; 39 Items (Box 8)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary, 1927-1930; 31 Items (Box 8)
      - Liberian Boundary Chief Commissioner Report, 1912-1913; 5 Items (Box 9)
      - Liberian Boundary Chief Commissioner, 1912-1919; 31 Items (Box 9)
      - Liberian Boundary Chief Commissioner, 1911-May 1914; 34 Items (Box 9)
      - Liberian Boundary Chief Commissioner, 1915; 34 Items (Box 9)
      - Liberian Boundary Chief Commissioner, June-December 1914; 24 Items (Box 9)
      - Liberian Boundary Commission Maps, 1915; 14 Items (Box 9)
      - Liberian Boundary, 1950-1955; 5 Items (Box 9)
      - Minutes of Civil Commission to Sinoe, January-February 1917; 2 Items (Box 9)
      - Report of Frontier Claims Commission, 1932; 58 pp. (Box 9)
    - Subject Files (Box 9)
      - Boy Scouts Association enrollment card, n.d. (Box 9)
      - Census Summary, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
      - Franco-Danish Industrial Society, n.d. (Box 9)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary, 1958; 5 Items (Box 9)
      - Garvyism, n.d., 2 Items (Box 9)
        2 items
      - Historical Sketch of Political Condition in Sinoe from, 1884-1934 (Box 9)
      - History of the Franco-Liberian Boundary, 1907; 1945-1958 (Box 9)
      - Pledges Made by Cape Palmas Greboes on Restoration to their Town Sites, 1915 (Box 9)
      - Program for Celebration, July 26, 1938 (Box 9)
      - Reference Summaries of Sinoe County Record, 1892-1895 (Box 9)
      - Township Commissioner Certificate, 22 September 1977 (Box 9)
    - General Records (Box 9)
      - 1920-1930, 7 Items (Box 9)
      - Executive Office Records, 1930-1943; 2 Items (Box 9)
      - Other General Records, 1944-1948; 2 Items (Box 9)
      - True Whig Party Presidential Campaign, 1926-1928; 31 Items (Box 9)
  - Interior Department (Box 9)
    - Correspondence - General (Box 9)
      - 1913-1919, 5 Items (Box 9)
      - 1920-1943, 14 Items (Box 9)
      - France, 1924-1926; 37 Items (Box 9)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary Commission, 1912-1919; 3 Items (Box 9)
      - Secretary of the Interior, 1917-1919; 6 Items (Box 9)
    - Correspondence - Departmental (Box 9)
      - 1926-1940, 7 Items (Box 9)
      - Anglo-Franco-Liberian Bounday District Commissioner, 1920-1925; 35 Items (Box 9)
      - Bureau of Tribal Affairs, 1938-1941; 8 Items (Box 9)
      - Central Province, 1924-1936; 11 Items (Box 9)
      - Commissioner at Large, 1912-1916; 4 Items (Box 9)
      - Commissioner General, 1916-1919; 25 Items (Box 9)
      - Commissioner General, 1925-1926; 3 Items (Box 9)
      - Eastern Province District 1, 1935-1939; 9 Items (Box 9)
      - Eastern Province District 2, 1926-1942; 27 Items (Box 9)
      - Eastern Province District 3, 1934-1939; 18 Items (Box 9)
      - Grand Bassa, 1916-1930; 6 Items (Box 9)
      - Grand Bassa, 1931-1938; 14 Items (Box 9)
      - Grand Cape Mount, 1924-1943; 6 Items (Box 9)
      - Inspector General, 1924; 8 Items (Box 9)
      - Maryland County Superintendent, 1921-1935; 16 Items (Box 9)
      - Maryland ,, n.d., 1915-1920; 16 Items (Box 9)
      - Montserrado, 1931-1942; 7 Items (Box 9)
      - Sinoe County Special Commission,?, 1931-1932; 17 Items (Box 9)
      - Sinoe, 1915; 5 Items (Box 9)
      - Sinoe, 1930-1937; 18 (Box 9)
      - Sinoe, 1938-1943; 20 Items (Box 9)
      - Western Province, 1924-1940; 10 Items (Box 9)
      - Western Province, 1941-1944; 31 Items (Box 9)
    - General Records (Box 9)
      - , n.d., 1914-1924; 6 Items (Box 9)
      - , n.d., 1930-1939; 15 Items (Box 9)
      - Central Province, n.d., 1927-1941; 4 Items (Box 9)
      - Grand Bassa,, n.d., 1927-1952; 43 Items (Box 9)
      - Grand Cape Mount, 1924; 1944; 2 Items (Box 10)
      - Maryland,, n.d., 1916-1931; 15 Items (Box 10)
      - Maryland,, n.d., 1932-1939; 6 Items (Box 10)
      - Montserrado,, n.d., 1936; 1940; 55 Items (Box 10)
      - General Records, Sinoe, 1940 (Box 10)
      - Western Province, n.d., 1914-1929; 10 Items (Box 10)
      - Western Province, 1930-1939; 9 Items (Box 10)
      - Western Province, 1940-1942; 6 Items (Box 10)
  - Justice Department (Box 10)
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
      - Attorney General, 1925; 1931; 2 Items (Box 10)
  - State Department (Box 10)
    - Domestic Correspondence - Departmental (Box 10)
      - 1912-1917, 7 Items (Box 10)
      - 1918-1930, 11 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, 1912-1920; 16 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, 1921; 71 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, 1922-1924; 18 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, January-June 1925; 19 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, July 1925-1930; 18 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, 1931-1933; 21 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, January-March 1934; 17 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, April-December 1934; 68 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, 1935-1940; 2 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, 1941-1942; 41 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, 1943; 49 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, 1945-1946; 36 Items (Box 10)
      - Interior Department, 1947-1949; 63 Items (Box 10)
      - Central Province Gbarnga District, 1931-1968; 16 Items (Box 10)
      - Central Province Saniquelle District, 1934-1958; 16 Items (Box 10)
      - Central Province Gbarnga District, 1931-1968; 16 Items (Box 10)
      - Central Province Tapita and Kakata Districts, 1944-1949; 5 Items (Box 10)
      - Central Province, 1912-1919; 27 Items (Box 10)
      - Central Province, 1920-1922; 32 Items (Box 10)
      - Central Province, 1923-1930; 17 Items (Box 10)
      - Grand Bassa, 1916; 1933; 4 Items (Box 10)
      - Grand Cape Mount, 1911-1919; 19 Items (Box 10)
      - Grand Cape Mount, 1920-1930; 19 Items (Box 10)
      - Grand Cape Mount, 1931-1944; 6 Items (Box 10)
      - Grand Cape Mount, 1945-1951; 39 Items (Box 10)
      - Maryland, 1912-1919; 10 Items (Box 10)
      - Maryland, 1920-1929; 10 Items (Box 10)
      - Maryland, 1930-1944; 4 Items (Box 10)
      - Montserrado, 1922-1949; 7 Items (Box 10)
      - Sinoe, 1911-1919; 24 Items (Box 10)
      - Sinoe, 1920-1929; 23 Items (Box 10)
      - Sinoe, 1945-1959; 8 Items (Box 10)
      - Western Province, 1934; 1949; 6 Items (Box 11)
      - Justice Department, 1915-1945; 6 Items (Box 11)
      - Postmaster General, 1921-1930; 3 Items (Box 11)
      - Department of Public Works, 1945-1949; 5 Items (Box 11)
      - Treasury Department, 1915-1930; 6 Items (Box 11)
      - Treasury Department, 1940-1945; 8 Items (Box 11)
      - Customs Receivership, 1911-1922; 10 Items (Box 11)
      - Financial Advisor, 1945; 26 Items (Box 11)
      - War Department, 1912-1919; 33 Items (Box 11)
      - War Department, 1920; 15 Items (Box 11)
      - War Department, 1921-1927; 43 Items (Box 11)
      - War Department, 1930-1939; 19 Items (Box 11)
      - Secretary of War re: Eastern Province, 1920-1922; 13 Items (Box 11)
    - Domestic Correspondence - Legislative (Box 11)
      - 1919-1922, 2 Items (Box 11)
      - 1937-1938, 22 Items (Box 11)
    - Domestic Correspondence - Judicial (Box 11)
      - 1922, 1945-1948; 3 Items (Box 11)
    - Foreign Correspondence (Box 11)
      - , n.d., 1911-1912; 32 Items (Box 11)
      - January 1912-June 1914, 89 pp. (Box 11)
      - 1915-1930, 15 Items (Box 11)
      - 1931-1943, 3 Items (Box 11)
      - 1944-1979, 7 Items (Box 11)
      - 1915-1930, 15 Items (Box 11)
      - Belgium, 1911-1935; 4 Items (Box 11)
      - Canary Islands, 1913; 4 Items (Box 11)
      - Fernando Po (Equatorial Guinea), 1911-1935; 4 Items (Box 11)
      - France, 1915-1919; 6 Items (Box 11)
      - France, 1920-1925; 16 Items (Box 11)
      - France, Liberian Pleinpotentiary in Paris, 1923-1930; 5 Items (Box 11)
      - France, Liberian Representative in Paris, 1922-1925; 3 Items (Box 11)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary List of Documents, c. June 1956; 60 pp. (Box 11)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary Commission, 1911-1916; 16 Items (Box 11)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary, 1917-1919; 16 Items (Box 11)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary, 1946-1947; 9 Items (Box 11)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary, 1949-1956; 47 Items (Box 11)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary, part 1, 1958; 32 Items (Box 11)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary, part 2, 1958 (Box 11)
      - Franco-Liberian Boundary, January-August 1957; 14 Items (Box 11)
      - Anglo-Franco-Liberian Boundary Commission, part 1, 1920; 14 Items (Box 11)
      - Anglo-Franco-Liberian Boundary Commission, part 2, 1920 (Box 11)
      - Anglo-Franco-Liberian Boundary, September-December 1957; 12 Items (Box 11)
      - French Guinea, 1917-1919; 12 Items (Box 11)
      - Germany, Severence of Diplomatic Relations, 5 May 1917 (Box 11)
      - Gold Coast, 1952 (Box 11)
      - Great Britain, 1911-1920; 17 Items (Box 11)
      - Great Britain, 1931-1948; 4 Items (Box 11)
      - Great Britain, Anglo-Liberian Boundary Survey Records, 1927-1928; 6 Items (Box 12)
      - Great Britain, Anglo-Liberian Boundary Commission, 1911-1913; 19 Items (Box 12)
      - Great Britain, Anglo-Liberian Boundary, 1914; 49 pp. (Box 12)
      - Great Britain, Anglo-Franco-Liberian Boundary, 1919; 22 Items (Box 12)
      - Great Britain, Anglo-Liberian Boundary Survey, 1924; 18 Items (Box 12)
      - Great Britain, Anglo-Liberian Boundary Survey, 1925; 18 Items (Box 12)
      - Great Britain, Liberian Consulate General in England, 1930-1940; 4 Items (Box 12)
      - League of Nations, 1928-1934; 11 Items (Box 12)
      - Liberian Boundary Survey, 1921-1923 (Box 12)
      - Liberian Boundary Survey, 1926-1926; 30 Items (Box 12)
      - Liberian Boundary Survey, 1926-1927; 58 Items (Box 12)
      - Liberian Boundary Survey, 1928-1930; 42 Items (Box 12)
      - Liberian Consul General in England, 1913; 11 Items (Box 12)
      - Panama, 1921 (Box 12)
      - United States, 1912-1949; 8 Items (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
      - General Records, n.d., 1968-1969; 3 Items (Box 12)
      - Bureau of Information, 1922-1961; 8 Items (Box 12)
  - Treasury Department (Box 12)
    - Correspondence (Box 12)
      - 1911-1949, 8 Items (Box 12)
      - Bureau of Audits, 1938; 2 Items (Box 12)
      - Bureau of Internal Revenue, 1912-1942; 16 Items (Box 12)
      - Customs Receivership, 1914-1930; 10 Items (Box 12)
      - Financial Advisor1941-1945, 1915; 3 Items (Box 12)
      - Interior Department, 1924; 1930-1941; 19 Items (Box 12)
    - General Records (Box 12)
      - 1916-1933, 3 Items (Box 12)
      - Bureau of Internal Revenue, 1915-1983; 8 Items (Box 12)
      - Customs Receivership, 1934-1942; 9 Items (Box 12)
  - War Department (Box 12)
    - Correspondence (Box 12)
      - 1916-1925, 22 Items (Box 12)
      - 1933-1937, 10 Items (Box 12)
      - History of the Liberian Army by G. Stanley Padmore, 1915; 66 pp. (Box 12)
      - Interior Department, 1917-1931; 25 Items (Box 12)
    - General Records (Box 12)
      - 1911-1935, 12 Items (Box 12)
      - Annual Reports, 1924-1941; 4 Items (Box 12)
- Legislative (Box 12)
  - Senate Journal (Box 12)
    - 27 Feb-13 Mar 1952, 54 pp. (Box 12)
      [MS]
    - 13 Oct 1952-11 Feb 1953, 48 pp. (Box 12)
    - 2 Mar-2 June 1953, 67 pp. (Box 12)
    - 26 Oct-9 Dec 1953, 54 pp. (Box 12)
    - 14-18 Dec 1953, 76 pp. (Box 12)
    - 4-8 Sept 1967, 27 pp. (Box 12)
    - 22 July-7 Aug 1968, 56 pp. (Box 12)
- Judicial (Box 12)
  - Supreme Court (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1914-1939; 12 Items (Box 12)
  - 1st Circuit, Montserrado Municipal Courts (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1936; 5 Items (Box 12)
  - 3rd Circuit Court (Sinoe) (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1914-1916; 3 Items (Box 12)
  - 4th Circuit Court (Maryland) (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1915; 1949; 2 Items (Box 12)
  - 1st Circuit Court (Grand Cape Mount) (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1917; 2 Items (Box 12)
  - 4th Circuit Court (Sinoe) (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1931-1942; 22 Items (Box 12)
  - Supreme Court (Box 12)
    - Records, 1983 (Box 12)
  - 2nd Circuit, Montserrado Municipal Courts (Box 12)
    - Records, 1915; 1930; 3 Items (Box 12)
  - Grand Bassa Probate Court (Box 12)
    - Records, 1924 (Box 12)
  - 5th Circuit Court (Maryland) (Box 12)
    - Records, 1927-1931; 4 Items (Box 12)
  - 5th Circuit Court (Sinoe) (Box 12)
    - Records, 1912-1937; 17 Items (Box 12)